You left a bit loud, but the timing ain't right, I checked my pulse, said maybe it's me,
but betters don't lie, they repeat like a beat, call it a sip, nah, playing chess while
they think it's a skit, dick, dick, noise I gave you, feel it shit, but you can't quite
All every fake laugh, confidence starting to bomb degrees.
That's where you fall.
I talked to Scribbles, and Scribbles wants another reading.
Like, I'll start a live later, because he was, like, at a Oingo Boingo or something
concert, and then him and his wife were like, oh, yeah, like, we want to do a reading.
And so Scribbles' IRL might be here later.
Like, that'd be pretty cool, but I just hope I don't get too drunk.
But I throw on their way home, I saw, so I don't think he's, like, too far from
venue or whatever, because I think he lives in, I'm not sure, Nevada or something, so.
but that'll be cool if he comes by and then I can do a reading for them.
Actually, I've been doing readings for people like actually people have been coming to my house
and stuff and ordering over the phone too and because it's the guy I got involved in that
was reading for somebody and I predicted the guy's death because I was like death and there's
like a lot of stuff unclear about it and like a lot of like maybe lies about it and I said there's
because of a curse and all this and then all this whole all this stuff and then it's like she's
of self-inflicted gunshot wound or whatever,
but they said that it was about a car accident.
I picked up the car too, but I was like,
that's like kind of like an illusion about that.
Yeah, until they lie about it at first and said it was.
So I would talk to like his ex-girlfriend
and then I talked to like another one of his ex-girlfriends.
Like all the ex-girlfriends are kind of getting together now.
And she's like, you wanna talk to this guy?
And so one of them talked to me on the phone.
The other one brought me over a few drinks a couple nights.
Went at it and like we just use few decks and it was fun. I mean it's I love doing tarot
It's it's kind of cool, but it's a kind of like now
It's like yeah, I mean it's like only the people that really really really like get it early understand. Hi, babe. Hi
Oh, there's Rudy. Yeah, and I'm her does continue. Hi, rude. How are you?
Hi
You're just coming over say hi
Yeah
Thank you so much. I mean it's like I mean I try to have a compassion for people too and I say I understand people and I say
I don't I don't want to really at the end of they hurt people's feelings and stuff
But I say I have to like fight back sometimes and like you know and I even if I'm in like the chats
I wasn't disrespecting her chat or whatever just now
I was on several alts and but then the person who's that boat as we get into go
Go Asia I'll explain like a person person is actually the name of a demon
And so that person who there's they're an Iranian person. It's like they're they devil and demonology
And it's like, you shouldn't know that like things like, you know, like, like,
Goetia symbols and the names of Goetia are being used on you in these chat rooms
and maybe bringing outsides of you because, you know, that he does like, I mean,
it's like that the personality doesn't fit with personality, right?
It's like, they're just terrible.
I mean, it's like, all I did was make them a mod here and like compliment them
because then you had a program nightbot.
That's all I ever did.
I never did anything wrong.
And this person is just constantly bad-mouthing me,
like, I'm almost done.
I mean, it's like, and then it's like,
oh, I love to see Seki with zero viewers.
Well, it's like, there's very rarely that happens,
but sometimes it does when I start the show.
So if you catch in the very beginning.
Sometimes they'll maybe piss everybody off and everyone will leave, but it's like, I don't think like, you know, it didn't happen that often.
It's like, so it's not like they're just acting like, oh, I just have zero, zero people and I have people here.
I mean, it is a little quiet because I know people are intimidated by these bullies because they're bullies, you know?
It's like, hi, Rudy. That's the loudest he meows. He doesn't have much in me. He's like 18 years old. He's an old man.
I can't, right? He's an old man. Hi, you're an old man, but you're very soft.
You're very soft and like, you know, you're very good looking. It's a very good looking cat. You're a great cat.
He's very loving too, right? You're a big loving cat. You're big. Oh, you're a big softie. Oh, you know you are
I'm gonna pay your back. I'm gonna pay your back
See all I can use all the cats. I mean it's like but I do more careful with the one that just came in after a year and a
Half because like you know
It's like yeah, he's a little bit wild and stuff like that
And so it's like but it's like, you know, it's a good time to say he's like, oh my gosh
He's like, you know, if you touch your cat, you know, they're saying you're an animal abuser
They call it I got called filthy animal abuser and all the stuff and it's like, you know
It's like that's like it's like kind of like that's the opposite just like it's like cyrox and I'm bold and stuff like that
And it's like, I'm obviously not,
I mean, and my hair's not greasy.
It's like, I got out of the shower.
They do occasionally take a bath and something,
my nails perfect, like no, they never usually are,
but you know, they're okay.
I mean, it's like, I'm just not this like monster or whatever.
I mean, I have to be some time, but you know, it's like,
but then it's like, are they showing their pictures?
No, they just have to come and criticize and like,
and then at the same time, they look like this.
Okay, they look like this.
That's what they look like, okay?
It's gonna be a great cartoon. I need to put your herd all this stuff tonight, but it'll be great
It'll be great. I love my long hair. I do love my long hair. Hey Rudy. What you're just sitting on my lap
You're just gonna sit on my lap like that
But you're just sitting on my lap
But I'm such a terrible person. I'm an animal abuser and I just use my cats for props
So, I mean, you know what? Why would you even like sit with me? Oh, you love me or something?
Hi, you're an old man. It's such an old man cat. Oh, you're happy. You see your wagging his tail
You're a happy cat. He like would be in Papa's lap like this. Yeah. Oh, they're animals. They're animals. Oh, they're not kids
They're animals
Yeah
So sweet. He's happy. He's a happy cat. He's a little old. He's old
I mean, it's like people say oh my cat looks like 17 16 years old. I'm like, oh my god
He's 18 like he's like an elderly cat and it's like and then he like, you know
He gets very like attached and he wants to be close and it's like
You know, I want him, you know, I just like, I get worried.
He's like, he's getting like close, you know,
and it's like, then that's where, oh, I don't know.
I kills him and, you know, I know,
I know that's already coming in and stuff like that.
Like, oh, baby, he's like, he's like the Lion King.
Very beautiful cat.
Yeah.
You're a good cat.
Okay.
What are you gonna do?
You're gonna sit there?
Okay.
Yeah.
And then when the door's over there,
the door's sleeping over there.
The door's over there.
We're gonna wake her up.
Oh, Marcy.
And the door's sleeping over there.
They're all sleeping.
There they are.
Yeah, there's all these blankets and stuff then like, you know
This chillin as usual. Hi, you're coming over here, Lenar. You're gonna come over and say hello. Oh
You want attention too? Okay? I mean, I'm not like I really am not like trying to like, you know
Say I'm like that great of a person or whatever
But at the end of the day, I do know my cats love me and I love my cats
That's like so it's like saying terrible things about me and my cats. It's like really
Out of pocket and people know like people don't really know me they didn't know that and so it's like they just are purely misleading and they'd like
It'd be like me calling somebody like
You know, but then they say oh, we can't talk about like kid
You know, it's like kids or and my pets aren't my kids
Even though that they're the closest thing I'll ever have the kids right and it's like so they are my kids
And it's basically also like, you know, I give like, you know
Just like you have it to give a teenager freedom and the cat's like a teenager. Oh, oh, you're fighting. Oh
But cat bite
Oh shit, but you're fighting with you're fighting with Rudy. No
Lenore he has you hissed
But hey, what do you do leave Rudy alone?
nor
Oh my god, my table. I'm so sorry
Lenore, I mean I have a piece of fish on the table man. I know I just had a piece of fish
Geez, thank you. No nurse. The nurse tails wagging right now. What are you here?
Are you plotting Lenore? Why are you plotting?
You're you looking you're plotting something over here
No, I come over ready. You want to come over? Okay. You can come over you can come over
There's no you so excited
Okay
They're like, oh, he's so skinny. You like making you're already home self chicken and I don't fry you know
I'm making I have um, I'm going to make now that you said that now. I'm hungry now. Oh, I just run my chat
Okay, it says um
I have a biscuits. I have like a biscuit sandwich kind of thing in the freezer. Oh my gosh. You're here. Okay. You're here
You're gonna say oh, he's so skinny, but he's like yeah, he's like an old man. He's like 18 years old
I mean, it's like he's so old
Not this I mean he's like he's very well fed taking care of they kept up all this food out right now
I mean that I'm interested in it. They always have food out, right?
So it's like they eat as they whatever they want to eat. It's not like they're like oh my god
The cats aren't eating cats eat before I do and you know, I do right
Like a massage like that you like that. Oh, oh, yeah. Oh like a massage
Yeah, so I've sad news is that Jamie and blocked me
You know she tried to are you making spread packets from chicken tender. Are you in jail?
Are you in prison or something?
Okay, I don't mix it spread packets. That's what they call things in the jail. They call them spreads. I don't I don't know
I just got that like I was like, what is that? Look at any beautiful?
Hi, beautiful. Yeah, let me see. I need to yeah, if you send
If you like because I'm not monetized right now
I do I did put together this like the first 300 chapters of I book the psychonomicon
With, most of them are illustrated, like a lot of them are, you know, it's fully illustrated with like, you know, rock and, you know, it costs quite a lot to make, but it's worth it because it's like the show and it's like every chapter is like an analysis and like three, like a three level analysis of each episode.
So the first three hundred chapters, I'm just doing on my show a special deal, which is like $5 and you just have to cash out me to $5 and then with your email address.
And then I'll send you the link to the PDF and then they'll be up
But you know, it's gotten a lot of good feedback right now
Knock stuff up my table. I can show you like a little bit over here
I can like look at the psychonomicon you can see so it's not like a bunch of BS. I'm telling you it's like
Fully documented how cool it is. Okay, let's have a look at my psychonomicon
Oh, Joe. There's Joe Shippley. Okay. Yes. Okay. Joe, I need to play the I need to play the I need to be here when I play it though
Get up. Get off here, Joe
And I'm gonna make my biscuit. I'm gonna make my biscuit dinner tonight. I like a biscuit and a dinner
You're gonna love this Joe. You're gonna love it
You know, it's really cool too. Oh, here's Joe. Okay. Hi Joe
Are you ready to see it?
I have the familiar words to say,
when you leave this world behind you,
it's what you'd see behind.
Remember that song is Three Wooded Crosses.
Hey, Joe, this is Dedicated To You.
There's a song dedicated to you.
Watch this real quick.
This is dedicated to you, your song.
Oh, hell yeah, remember you're trying to play it
on good size, I'm gonna hear it.
Thank you, sir.
Oh my god.
I already love it.
Hell yeah.
Grab it.
You better not be trolling me, this is like gay.
Game, come listen to this and see what you're playing.
If you're this gay or you're trolling me, what is this?
Come here, buddy. Listen to this.
Like, if you turn off, hold on, I'll try and get out. It's like, keep it playing.
Can you hear it, Dan?
It's like Ram style.
I love you.
I love you. Thank you. Thank you.
There's a nightmare waiting for you, I don't like it
No, it was dead
Don't care if it's better than you thinkin' even you're old
And he showed broo boots
It was like broo boots
It's hard to answer it all right now
That was good
The television flickers blue
Showing things that change me too
A laugh track at the blue
That's three minutes off, you're all dead
But nobody lives here
There's gone
Don't live way too many things
HA HA HA HA
It's too many things
What's in the dog?
Wake your dog like a robot
But I'll kill you
Oh it's getting like a rap song
Now it's a rap song
You didn't say role bro
I'm never...
You know we skated, but...
Sonny, I'm trying to tell Kim that you're gay, but like, you're not really gay, you're like, super gay.
You're like, super gay.
This is the best song I've ever heard that was the best song I've ever heard
See the lyrics like everywhere you look everywhere you go everywhere
I heard it trust me. I like that's like you. Thank you. I know you tried to play them good sides for me
Thank you, brother. I know I didn't he got mad and he kicked me off like I was a kind of bitch like he was like
Oh, I'm just trying to bleach off each of his show. I mean, it's like what the hell I was like trying to like I asked him several times
Can you play for like 10 seconds to get here?
You know, it's okay, you're not saying one thing that's gay not you because you're a good gay guy or a cool gay guy
Well, like, you know, it's really gay.
Like the people that come on alts in your chat, like, I don't
want to say, you know, it's really me.
So I'll just come on an auto Saturday night.
Like, make a fuck you, Black RG.
Fuck it back.
Is that who is the speedier?
Or who is that?
Who's Black RG?
I'm just saying, man, these fucking alts, like you imagine
seeing one time Black RG did aggravate me when he's like, I
sold modest Mousin concert.
Like, I would kill myself for ever.
So modest Mousin concert.
Yeah, it's exactly it's like a retarded British bit. Yeah, like wow
I see modest mouse like you know, you couldn't pay me money to go see
ATPC you're at you're at like a
Having made it that list or anything. I'd rather see Goo Goo dolls than fucking
Modest
In our scribbles, you know who scribbles is right? He has like fuck
Yeah, yeah
I was in his chat tonight. He wants to get a reading from him. I come tonight. He said he wants to get a reading
but um
They're at a little point go concert like on the outside of the tent
Like I'm your friend and I've been here for you and like I don't get a reading like what about my reading like what about me?
I will
Now you're gonna say you're gonna be rude
can't get in there.
I think it's rude.
No, no, I think it's very seriously, actually, I actually was, but I do-
You weren't saying like, oh, I pulled the gayest card, and it's for you.
Yeah.
Like, I know what you're gonna do.
Right.
I know what you're gonna do.
I'm gonna say, you know, you're gonna come move in with me.
I already know my future.
I don't need your cards.
You're like, do you want to move in with me?
Hey, can you check up Chris K?
I think Chris K needs a place to stay.
I said, I'll change that.
I know James moves here, and it's a water vault, because she's going to go to the water
vaults, and remember-
Here's Kate as chatterbait with me.
I'll let him live with me for a month.
Oh.
Anyway, it has to do with every day, though.
It has to do with every day
we just have to be naked in my house.
Like, don't chatter.
Well, that's chatterbait with my dad.
No, because like I would say they're women and watching me, but you don't know who's watching
But then it's like, you know, you're just like they're then they give you tokens and stuff like that
You're like you're like a ski ball machine kind of but you're naked
This thing I fucking hate saying is like these fucking retards that join beaters free with Sam
They not say I like Sam bad. I just can't stand be there, but Sam is
No, listen man
But like they're all scared to come up on psyche straight. I'll join psyche anytime that link is dropped. It's like he's a real dude
Thank you. Well, we're all right. Oh, thank you. Thank you very much. Can't be over. No, but you know what?
No, wait, but bother me is like and I don't want to bring up the story because it's like it sounds like some kind of innocent story
You're telling on a show one night and then they brought it up. There's a lot of oh, yeah
And they're like, oh really he's and then they're like saying kind of stuff about you and I was like
I know it's like I mean, how dare they I mean it's like and it's like I mean the people just go so far and it's like obviously
Let me tell the stories they said about you motherfucker
Sam I've heard them all they're terrible
I'm not saying, I'm not going to tell those,
I'm not going to tell those stories.
I'm not going to talk shit about people
when they're not around and defend themselves
because they don't feel big.
Got it.
Joe, Joe, I'm not going to improve the story
or whatever it was, but I'll just say.
Or I'll call the, I'll say, yo.
You can say whatever you want.
No, of course I won't.
I'm not going to insinuate that even,
because it's like, I know you, and I say,
I know you're not like, and I say,
they should know you too,
but they're all sitting there tripping,
sipping, beating, and they're like,
oh my gosh, is this true?
We have to listen to, we have to know,
this is Joe this is like Joe who we love and it's like why are we treating people like this
i mean i didn't mean to bring anything i'm just saying it was like wow we're just saying wild
shit i think people are job i think people like beata and christine and sweepy they never had
friends like in school so like now that they're 50 they're like they got their group they got their
Right, they don't have the balls
Oh, well, I'm now I'm straight because I don't like them
They guys are clean and like, you know, I'd have like you know good fashion says I'm like, you know, they're actually that's against the Bible
Our gay people were burning hell yes. Oh what?
if God made everybody in his
image and he created gay people
too because um if he created
all people who packed my gay
bone. I like that. I have I
have we I guess we tonight too
with you. It's for you. Oh, do
you mind if I do weed on your
panel? I don't know.
Thank you. Oh, this is the
we didn't run over. We're here
for you. So, okay, here we
go.
now Joe we have someone backstage named the crazy n-word
Do I even bother?
That's you 45. That's cute. Okay, but he's gonna say the n-word or something. I mean, I mean, what is he gonna do?
You've been so let me just put a book
Give him a chance though. They say what oh, what is that guy name? What is that cat's name?
Rudy has Rudy right there. Oh
Rudy kind of love you, Rudy. He's an old man.
He's old man. Yeah, let him I'll let him on hold on a second. He's like 18 years old
He's like 18 years old, okay, he's back
Oh
Swear to God he's 18 so you don't lie
Who are you are cat years? Oh, no, it's like you never like in dog years like a dog's three
What is cat years? It's like one year is like I swear to God. I've never had a cat. I'm not eating
Yeah. Well, crazy. and we're
it's one to five years for
years. That year. They left.
Don't let it. Don't let that
like I tried to join beat is the other day she's like oh Joel you're too drunk
you're too drunk like they can look at look at the fucking mirror you'll bitch
yeah my god oh my god and the Christians like I'll beat it as a drake and
oh my god do you know oh did you see the fucking fight that Christine in
summer had that was fucking good so Christine is the fucking Christine the
drama started class a whore or yeah sure yeah I mean she totally is drama
Right and summer is like good at defending yourself and stuff and then like, you know, trying to be guilt-shipped and oh
You didn't stand up for me. No, but Edward Island. I know a while if you was there
I guarantee you that Christine reports fetus channel in the back
I guarantee you like even though Christine acts like she's being disfriend. I guarantee you she bugger reports or shit
Well, I mean I need to get her baby. So she can laugh. I don't care anymore. You were sure here
Yeah, I watch it. Yeah, I did. I mean, did you see this video? Oh, look at this. Look, you're missing it, you blinked.
Oh, I see it. You see it? You saw it? That was Tabra. That was Tabra. That's Samman. Oh, come on.
That's a little too bad. I like him too. I always said I like him. I mean, I don't like him, but I like him.
Now, Bita, that's, can I say bitch? Yeah. You might have a say the word bitch.
Oh Kim you like Bita? She's a bitch. Oh I love you Kim. Oh you're a dick.
Oh yeah like I never even know like I swear to God the first time Bita ever saw a kid
she's like I love you. I love you. It's like you never even know her. How the fuck do you
love somebody you never ever fucking met. Oh I love you. You're disgusting.
I love her, I love her leader, all right, aww, psyche, that was a little too much, that was a little too much.
Why is your cat so an asshole? Why is your cat literally so an asshole?
Because you're being an asshole.
God, like Jesus Christ, I get it, cat, you worked out, like don't show off.
Your cat is showing you his asshole because he's reading your dog.
No, I swear to God, the cat was like, then they're like, they're reading your dog.
You wouldn't get me off like you can't me home. I know I'm thinking a little bit like I give good times anxiety
Kissing and trans at your studio we want that I'm so tired of people not liking you would not join your stream
So I wanted to join let's see if this is all this is all the kissing and trans is on the air. Oh
Memorandum already drank a cup of Saints piss. I
Can look at take off one second. There you go
That was it that was it you saw it, okay
So that's three cigarettes plus two what's two plus three cigarettes
five. Five cigarettes. It's
two point three. Hey baby.
Oh, that's Rudy. Rudy's an
old man. Hey, Kate's the
chef. Remember Lenore? Lenore's
my favorite cat though. Lenore's
like right now. Look at Lenore
right now. This is her right
The hell yeah, it's like
now.
Oh look she really is
You're better than me now Wow you're a cat you're actually better than me that you can't even speak English
Well neither can be to actually so good cat. Love you
But it's just someone named ice. Oh, no Joe someone says that true Joe. Yeah, okay, so there and then you wanna see Lola
Look at Lola. Hello, Lola. Are you there?
Lola
We're not burning joint. How do you Nick? We're not burning joint. She said burning joints always here white dog
What's good?
Yeah
RIP die back Darryl fucking Nick or burn a joint
He died
Did that make their own died fucking 22 years?
Chris I've only ever cracked rock Chris and that's just because the name is so
Don't compare crack rock for us at Dimebag. You know who it is. Hey Joe, you know where where is Chris K though?
I want to do a chatter bait with them
I'd have no idea where Chris came probably get knocked out by a little black midget like he did in that video
Let's watch it
I'll watch this I won't came to see it too. It's Kim's like sitting back like I'm not watching nothing look at me
And she is like I'm not gonna watch
You're a part of this line straight you're gonna come with me is like
Got sorry about that psyche.
Sorry she's like so hard to have fun with.
It's okay, it's okay.
Let me see.
I'm not hard to have fun with.
No, you know what?
It's not okay, actually.
It's actually not okay.
Cam, I'm so sorry.
Good, just send me then.
If it's so bad.
Oh, look at her gay purse.
Have you ever seen this?
Can you give me my purse?
Look at this, like wow.
Like, is it, can it give any gayer?
At least I got pride.
Wow, did you get that from Sandman?
Looks like Sandman's.
Pride?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You know what I'm saying?
Hey, don't get this super fuckin' fool, partner.
You better check yourself.
What are you doing, buddy?
I ain't no pussy.
Now, do you know what camera do all that?
I ain't no front-rope.
You better check yourself.
I don't give a fuck where you going to check.
Check yourself, partner.
Shit.
Hey.
You can't brush it.
Tap it.
What are you talking about?
Winner at once.
Man, what's up?
Look at this.
What's up?
What's happening?
What's up, man?
What's up?
Yeah, we're trying to get to it
Yeah
You're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you're gonna check it, you
He did he did he's like, what'd you thought about Chris or whatever, but you know what schools like you?
I don't think Sam here's either losses channel that whore crystal report his channel. She can kiss my fucking red
He does
two-foldish pride. Turn out the last competition. That's why the people
weren't laughing about the statement animation.
The stubborn souls of the losers here tonight.
Look at Chris K as our generation spends in the codecs like I
Know psyche Kim always hold on let me turn my camera like me for one second Kim always thought I gave a fuck about you
I don't give a fuck about both
Bye
If you don't want to hear me by, we're in my house.
When you're in my house, I can pass it one day.
When you're in my house.
All right, I'll take it.
Yeah, I'm going to take Chris K in the Oracle,
and then I have to go enter.
I'm going to search in the archive right now.
OK, so, um, yeah, well, the bridge is.
Archive, Chris K, the signal is regulatory.
He surfaces as a panel discussion transcript
through episode 428.
Reference is someone who is an excellent speaker who claims to like.
The record shows him as a controversial streamer from California with a document in history of
articulating white supremacist ideology, a name spoken in the archive's margins.
Neither guest nor through line, but through a presence noted and marked.
He appears four times across late night open panels,
existing at the periphery of the coast documented testimonies.
Chris K exists in the archive, not as a participant, but as a warning.
Oh, that was cold. That was cool.
Damn, it got his number. I wonder if Kim's in the arc.
That'd be honest, like the codex is one of the coolest things.
You love it?
It's really cool.
I mean, I love it, but I love it, but I love it, man.
The codex, if you want to support, I have, like, the first 300 chapters of the
second Omicron, which is all my, all the episodes described in, like, analyzed.
No, I don't want that. I don't want that.
Oh, okay, okay.
I don't want the, uh, the, what's it called, the first three chapters of the NamaCon?
Oh, 300 chapters?
They're 300 illustrated chapters of the Psychinoma.
Oh, no, no, no, no. I can barely read a sentence. Let it load 300.
That's our pictures.
Let's take a picture of you.
Yeah, pictures for the morons.
Like, can I get a burresque, though?
Thank you for asking at least.
Oh, I wasn't asking. I was telling you.
You better get to buy one of your iraq.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Hello?
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
For both to cover both of you. Oh, so it's free. But after you play it, we got to say you $10. So it's free
Yeah
Really
That's fair, okay, I'm gonna send it
I'll say your turn box out on I'll say your 10 bucks if you get named who's on the $10 bill who's on the $10 bill
I'll say uh
what is that it's not not my favorite is oh hold on this is like um we see it's too long
too long how much jefferson oh come on stop it is that what did you just look at a ten dollar bill
ten hamilton or something alexander hamilton ten hamilton is a singer
Oh my gosh, okay. Do you want to watch some more fights on a rumble or something or no?
No, I was over do so because there was like I played these girls fighting
They're not on rumble and then it's like then I saw like some titties
So I can't really play that one but I can like oh I can like about the trip because trip
I could up these fighting videos of me
Hey, we're one of Trisha. Let's just get kicked out of a concert like I think Alex is calling her trash delicious now or no bitch
Delicious
You want to see the bitchalicious, or are you going to kick out of the concert?
I don't want to see her kick me out of a concert.
You want to see that?
You do?
Okay.
Hell yeah.
I'll find it right now.
I'm looking for it.
Okay.
Where's that one to see?
Two, three.
Are there salmon with a hook?
Oh, I got it. I see a black eye in a dancing. There's so many great classic episodes here. Mike's trope off. Oh my gosh. Okay, so where is this?
Looking back there's a guy
There be his keys versus flirty diamonds. That was a good one
The high ones to grab your night back more the whole fuck
I found the trishelicious one here on the trishelicious, right?
This is her we think that a concert uncensored
I'm here brother, where's the video?
And imagine being stuck up and you're from fucking New Mexico.
It was probably the five foot tall hat that got me down.
That's not gonna fly here.
That's not how we get down in LA, bitch.
This is actual IRL, bitch.
Figure the fuck out.
Yeah, you do not know that.
You're nobody. You're nobody from fucking New Mexico, bitch.
That was that's why you're never gonna make it anywhere, bitch
That's why you're fucking nobody. You're a stupid fucking bitch
Nobody fucking likes you. I don't give a fuck. I don't
I don't care about this color. I care about the way you look. I was nice him and he fucking treated me like shit
So that's why you don't fucking deserve to have anything ever, ever, cause you're a bitch.
Well said, Trisha.
Cause I don't know, you're a very handsome man, I'm just asking.
I have a lot of lady friends, I'm a live streamer.
Yeah, are you streaming right now?
I'm live streaming right now, yeah, I have like 500 people in here.
I have 22 people in here.
YouTube nobody cares. Nobody knows who Tesla is. I'm trying to make him a famous worldwide name
I'm trying to get it out of Albuquerque. Yo
I know but we're trying to keep it. We're trying to keep we're trying to keep it pimping homie. I'm saying
Take her out. Hey, shut the fuck up because you know what?
I'm having fun
Yeah, that's what's up. That's why I came all the way here
You're weird man, you know you're mad fucking weird
This motherfucker mad weird look at her what's your name?
We're gonna refind him look at him
He's tall he thinks he's too good
Then you pause this
Yeah
Let's be active like that
Why don't I get a kiss on my cheek? Where's my kiss
Oh, hey
We're just watching Trisha. Let's just get kicked out of a concert. Okay
I like watching her tan her ass cheeks when she's
Guys a little bit weird
But it's okay, we're gonna make him and tell everybody how weird he is.
He don't want to be Chris Brown.
Okay, team of Chris Brown, see you later.
See you guys tomorrow.
Have a good night.
The fuck, get some fucking water.
Talk about, like, maybe you should fuckin' grow the fuck up and grow some balls, and we're
happy at fuckin' adults!
Oh my gosh, we three here, we're at first!
Am I on a bridge, bro?
Stop being a fucking high-duty bitch!
I'm growing up, don't watch!
I'm telling Kessels!
I'm never gonna, you know what this is reflecting badly on Chesley because you're about to get around this mess bar at all, this mess bar.
This guy is really weird, uncomfortable.
everybody's looking at her like everybody was looking at her like what the fuck is wrong with this
I get obnoxious sometimes what I'm with unlike
yo I'll tell you one thing Trishalicious is 10 times sexier and 10 times better and more funny than Bita
so hey Bita go fuck yourself you old cat bitch
Trishalicious is way cooler than me
this guy and yeah
Bita would have worked
He says, he says, Joe, I Joe, I G is here at heart.
It's Saturday.
I don't have to listen.
It's like, I don't have to work tomorrow.
So I did ask him just now, like, am I acting?
Am I acting a little too crazy?
Like, if I'm being crazy, just say it.
You know, I had four white gloss tonight, Joe.
And I'm like, you know.
I'm not even drunk. Yeah, I'm like, what the hell?
All right, so he basically asked me to leave.
All right, I got you.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I want you to stop.
I didn't kick her. Yeah, they kicked her out. Hey, great boy. Hey there's, hey there, INX is here. Do you want to say hi to Karrick or INX?
Oh, hi, great boy. What's his name? Great boy. Nice to meet you. Great boy. INX. She's awesome.
Hey, do you want to see me? I am gonna come down. It's like you.
Hey, Joe, do you want to take
Oh, she's coming to say hi.
I'm a love of you walk your past.
Were you about to ask me to be the walker?
Yeah, he said I had a nice voice before.
So how are you, psyche?
I said you had a sexy voice, baby.
You got a sexy voice.
Thanks.
Oh, hey sake, how are you doing? So you're not a date over 20?
Oh, I'm older. I'm older.
Yeah, I love your cat Lola like I said
I love animals. They're all adorable. Look how cute they are.
Yeah.
Look, there's Rudy right there. Rudy is sitting next to me. He's watching her.
He's the old man cat. I took him in last year.
his parents or his mom was like, you know, moving away
and she was gonna be like, you know, out a lot.
And so she, he's like, older cat.
And so she's like, well, do you mind taking him?
You know, and then it's like, and then he came over,
she got him into the carrier,
she put some calming treats or whatever in it.
And then he got in the carrier
and then she was crying on the phone.
She's like, what do I do?
And I was like, we'll bring him over here.
And she was like, and I was like, yeah,
you got him in the carrier.
It's like, now or never, you know?
and so she she drove over brought him over she was crying and she was like am i doing the right thing
i don't know i feel like i'm a bad mom and stuff and i was like no i'm not happy with me and he
they moved in he's like so happy he's like very he's very loving he's like a little bit older
he's like probably 18 years old now but he's a sweet he's 18 years old 18 he's old yeah kitty was 20
Yeah, I mean, he's at the end, you know, he's at like, you know,
the 20 year old, Lori or what's your name? Not Lori. What's your
name, sweetheart? I go by
I go by the name on there grateful. I next I was on an X. I used to go by on it
Do you hear rainbow? She had its 20 year old? What was your 20 year old cat 20 year old cat kitty?
It was a rescue from outside
Kitty kitty. I called her kitty. She was my first cap. I'm a I'm a picky-diss owner
I
What did she say
Well, so wait a minute they live till 25 or how old
25 is a little like your mark. That's a little crazy
Yeah, I think I heard that before because dogs only make it up to 12 13 small breeds do and then the bigger dogs
But in dog years like 12 times 7 she was 96 years old, but we had a picnics that lived till she was 18 years old
Oh, yeah, see the Pekingese by the volcano because she says I'm at her a dog in Hawaii or something
I pay Karen like oh, no, it's like you did that. That's that's an AI Pekingese picture
He made with a volcano in the back
I would give me it give me something to make an AI for you tonight. Like what do you want me to make a picture of right now?
Yeah, I like dogs. I'm gonna I'll send you some pictures of my Pekingese is maybe you can put them in AI
Another Pekingese picture background. Yeah
or where do you want the Pecanese to be and like what we're doing, whatever you put in the background
Okay, but wait a minute. Can you do an AI of them talking or something?
I remember somebody did that for me before and I still have it way below when when
Oh
I'm doing I'm doing a sandman cartoon inx. I want you to see me
Oh, yeah, I want to see that.
Yeah, what is this?
Ladies, David.
If I could ask, I forget.
Yeah, I went by a great.
Oh, that's what you made.
Well, that's so cool.
The A.I.
Cartoon. Yeah.
It's a good.
Oh, my God.
That's so good.
Don, come on.
I like said, man.
What is this?
What the hell is this?
That's him.
What's that, Kim?
Can I get a beer, please?
I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared
that's what is it going so soft to he's so soft like it's yeah, he's very cold
You know I was just on the Cates panel man
What is it why I remember she got mad because I I support you psyche. She's a trouble maker
She wants me to blast her out. I will Barry always told us he's terrified of her
So, I mean she's something else and then Jersey court has her full records up there with
She wants me to go at her like that I will
Remember
Yeah, I remember she was afraid of Rick before, you know, just the way because she keeps bringing my name up
They told me they somebody sent me a little clip of her talking to crystal Marie
And brings up my name all the time. So maybe she should come up again
And I mean
They're saying you look a little ridiculously skinny big dog. Sorry. Who?
He's he's not that
about psyche. That's the old man on panel. Oh yeah it was Rudy the skill man too. Rudy is the
Rudy's the skill. Oh Rudy! Rudy! I love you Rudy! Oh look at her saying I love you. She heard me.
She said no. She heard me saying I love her. I love you Rudy. Come on. Do you have pets Joe?
I don't, I used to have a dog into its eye, but I have like pet, I have a pet's heart.
I have the heart of a pet lover.
That's what I'm saying.
I know.
I did a great job on this one, but you can tell me how you like it, right?
I actually told the doctor to take Raven's heart out of his body and put it into my body.
So I actually have a dog's heart, okay?
Oh, there was like that, that pecanese.
That looks like one of our pecaneses that we had before, kind of blondish like that.
Foo Man 2 was his name.
And I don't camera. So have you ever seen Martha Stewart's dogs Mark? Have you ever seen Martha Stewart in the makeup?
I guess like shit's Ken at the point a coin. Here's in those pictures. Like, uh, there's a makeup artist
He's a gay guy hid giant his his name is Kenneth the coin
And he like
You know
So
Yeah, they're unrecognizable as like their their media stuff and almost you saw a different
I'll share his Martha Stewart picture. Well, this is a real you know
um
Elizabeth Taylor had a pecan ease but before she passed away that she had a different kind of dog the white dog
I forgot what the breed what that was called
Right, I mean somebody else has a pecan ease and I forget who it who it is
Look at this picture. Oh, look at this picture. I think you like this one here. This is but this is a real photo. This is yeah
Oh, really? Yeah. Oh, did you know there's a documentary that just came out about what
what the police are saying now about Marilyn Monroe when they when they did their investigation
and pictures everything they looked at. Yeah. And that documentary is about to come out,
Well, yeah, there was no water.
There was no water there for her to deal with.
There's no glass of water or picture of water or nothing.
And it looked like they set up her body like that.
They just put her on the bed.
I mean, it's like, um, so many things, like Joe DiMaggio, and she's already done that, like, stripped, she's the president at that point. Remember? She did that.
Like, she's like, happy birthday, Mr. President. Remember that thing?
That's who they think is behind her, uh, being gone is the Kennedys, not, not her exes or anything, because she was having an affair with Bobby, too, besides the president.
Okay, I'm gonna do like...
You said that song.
Happy birthday
Yeah
I'm gonna do a special picture for you with pecanese dogs. Okay. Oh, okay. Yeah. Okay. Cool. Yeah, right now for
Decades you like what's a decade is your favorite decade?
Decade I'd have to say the 90s, I guess early 90s or 80 70s
No, I was a little kid. I was too little then at the 80s when I went when I was older 80s because I was into the new wave all that music
Joe listen you're she's gonna love this okay, so this is special for you fine
Like new wave that that kind of music like trans music are they they had different names for it
Yeah, it's a real good grave. Check this out. Oh
How cute oh
Peek-a-Bee's is I'll take down the I'll take down the comment. That's the cutest thing I've ever done
Saw a dog wearing like black pants
So someone Karen was yeah, I'm wearing what photos
Everyone someone says Karen or sorry. They think it was Barry sharing what photos and it says psyche
You got cribkeeper arms says what if Barry sends you sends you a minx? No
I mean people gonna be messy like that. Then I'll do the same. I mean, you know, it's ridiculous. I keep everything
Yeah
So yeah, I just other one I have to post it
She needs to shut up because she keeps bringing my name up all the time and somebody even sent me a little clip
You know, I was doing something else and then they kept messaging me
Um, so yeah, I just stupid and she keeps bringing my name up and she isn't like her name being brought up with her
You know with with her being a wheelchair her son all of that
You know just leave my name out of your mouth because she's messy as hell
Yeah
Roller is all the clip
Oh my gosh, Joe. Yeah, they show that and then Crystal acts like she's cool with me. She I love
Ion eggs or whatever. That's what she was saying on panels and Kate's trying to get her to come at me
Do you think about her and ain't she midnight and then earlier she brought me up about something else
You know, so she wants to be brought up because I have a lot and I'll do that and that was from just another streamer
That she's been afraid of
I
Was over a Kate's channel earlier and I got kicked out and she was just laughing about it. Oh, you heard her. Yeah, I heard that
Yes, I mean I was just being friendly ridiculous. I was just kind of like trying to make banter
I wasn't even saying anything against her. I was like I was kind of making fun of Sandman a little bit
My dogs are the best dogs are the best
I always used to say that until the first rescue cat that I
Took in and I love all animals now and dogs and cats too, right?
They put all these, they put all these like 30 or 40 cats in FedEx boxes and like left them outside of the shelter.
Oh my God!
Are you serious?
Don't ever say that.
I was looking for my cat, like one of my cats and I went to the shelter that day and I was like but then but there was on the news
and so there were so many people came to the shelter that day that every cat was adopted.
And so I was like, kind of like, you know, but it's like, yeah, so it's a good publicity for these places.
If they even if it's like, you know, these bad stories, like it's like that people will say,
you know, say, oh, I need to go down there. And then they all get adopted in a day, like 34 cast.
Good, I'm glad. Because that's sad, though, you know, these people dumping their
animals in
Lady I did hear that the dog King Corsos are the gay is like that dogs are actually homosexual
So whoever the chat said they had a King Corsos your dogs gay
I've never heard that. I don't think any dog is
I've actually just made it up. I just made it
Yeah, I think I mentioned something about this they're called King Corsos dogs
I think the big dogs are big. It's a big breed. I think
I don't I don't think I know they're real tough dogs or they use them not for cattle
But I think for herding or something some kind of goats or something like see dogs like sheep dogs
Yeah
Okay, we'll do this. I mean it might not because it has to do what we'll see if it does it. Oh, it's it's generating it
Okay, so see okay, see if you like this one. Okay, so guys you said are you said these are gay dogs?
Joe because look I never said that I never
That's what they look like no that thought they were Huskier like oh, that's a golden collie
Yeah, this one's a King Corsa. Okay, but those are it, right?
Oh, that's a dog. There's a King Corsa.
It's the King Corso pride parade his dogs
You like that picture
Beautiful women there. That's their dog little fella. They're so cute. Oh look at me a big tall sexy Rob
Oh, they're easy double women. I'm now about look at the women. I guess there's that one look with her belly button
Yeah, she's not real.
The things out there hold me a little laugh, but she's not real.
These are computer-generated women and dogs.
I mean, nothing is real that you see.
Did you just make that? You just made that now?
Or you already had that picture?
I mean, that is now.
Oh, wow, that was quick.
No, you guys did not.
You did not.
I was in car so quickly.
You did not do that in one second.
I made that that fast.
Made that that fast.
In one second.
You did not.
Where did you go?
You made it.
I did.
Joe, what do you want me to make?
I made it.
What kind of dog?
I don't know.
I don't know what you make anything.
I don't know what you make.
Hold on. How about a Norwegian l count that we had one when I was in high school
Norwegian what alcal Norwegian l count l count we had one when I was in high school
Okay
What back in the 1940s? No, I wasn't born then my mom was born my mom was born in
Joe my mom was born when you were in the 1940s
That's when my mom was born
Yeah, Joe from the 1940s Joe. I have a picture of Joe with this L count. Yeah
No, she was born like the coast of the mid 40s my mom. I have a picture of Joe in the L count here. We go
See those are pretty dogs aren't they ours was
My arms are a little bit bigger
You know, even a cat you can you go big Rob is that you're trying to see when I eat my pussy?
Save it for my cats, please
Um
What's that ladies name whoever you are one thing I do regret
Call me grateful or
I'm sorry. Can you can you find another picture of Norwegian Elkhound because they're more hairier. They kind of look like the Husky
Okay, but they do have that mark on the back way better than that. I'm way fucking better looking
Okay, hold on there here. Okay
Okay, let me see if I got oh shit, huh? Okay Norwegian Elkhound. Okay. I got it. Okay. This is called some magic
Okay
I love the king robbers in chat so I'll be the night, but but you're going up.
Well, I got it.
I got it.
Let me see if I got this.
Oh, so that was a little bit.
That was a little bit.
So it refused our request.
Let me see if it will do this one.
Okay.
No, it's going to do this one.
So are you ready?
So this is actually Joe with the Norwegian.
Yeah.
I got a perfect now.
Okay.
We're waiting. I'm ready for it. Oh
God, what the hell is that?
Is that my Aunt Kathy? Hold on. That's my Aunt Kathy.
You don't even know her carrots.
What the hell? I'll just find that picture.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I can't I'm sorry. I'm so sorry guys. There you go. You need better apologize. Oh my gosh. I'm so sorry
This is fun. I can do more. I can do more. How about like how all of us holding hands? Okay. I can say skinny white guy
I'd like to see more Norwegian Elcounds
I think that his name was Olaf
Okay, Norwegian Elcound
I'm gonna say big
Yeah, they're very good furry. They have like thick hair. They're like fur, not hair, fur.
Oh, Olaf? Okay.
Olaf was his name. Oh, L-A-D, Olaf with a B on the end.
Oh, a lot. It's like he's...
Yeah, that was a Norwegian name my dad gave him.
My skeleton arms, my skeleton arms, I made it in Germany.
Norway then, they're from Norway, I'm from Norway.
I know, but he went to, he visited Germany for the last time.
There's a little crown a little doggy crap. No, that's a hat
Norwegian hat I think
That's a Norwegian
They're from Norway
No, that dog has a little smile as they zoom out
That's what they call in the L count
Hey, that's what they did.
It's Elkow.
Is that Norquow?
Oh, sorry.
Look at it.
They're saying about you, Joe.
He said, I knew I would find Joe.
Oh, my God.
I swear to God.
My eyes are too little.
Let me try to read that.
It's so tiny.
I know I would.
back to Joe
Look, why are you gonna say that when we're looking at the cutest dog with the cutest smile you ever saw George grow up?
No, come on. Look at her talk. We're all sweet
We're reaching out of town. Let me see again. Do another one. Let me see
Is it B2B and drunk and crying?
Yeah. Do you want to watch one of those? That'd be funny. Hold on.
Oh, yeah. I want to watch Betacrafts and Cry. She calls me drunk.
Well, you do the doobie. You do the doobie.
No, that's kind of mean. Why keep on with that though?
You were...
Get your old 50s lady off.
Joey, you're cool with her when you get on panel, Joe.
I know it's okay
If you want to do it, he wants you to do it. It's fine. I'm just not, you know
We didn't look at stroke off on the panel or Victoria. Let me see a horn. Oh, yeah, let's make one a struggle when he broke
Let's see me crash out on their panel here. Here's me. I'm in this one. Okay. Okay. Oh
this would be perfect don't do it it's like don't sacrifice yourself no you'll
love it i'll sacrifice myself i better love this
okay you'll love it you'll love it okay so here we go
let me just snap to the big dog okay
that's you you as michael michael jackson i see him but i don't hear it
Hey there, there's Psyche, Thriller.
Aw.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
You wish you were that handsome, Psyche.
You wish.
Motherfucker.
Thriller.
Why is there no volume?
Is it a song?
Is it a Michael Jackson song?
Should be playing.
It's a clip.
He said he was playing a clip.
I don't know if he has the sound off or the clip doesn't
have sound.
I don't know.
I don't care.
We can't hear you, Psyche.
Now we hear you, but we didn't hear it. No, we couldn't hear anything at your sound. You keep going out
We saw it. It was pretty cool to watch, but we just didn't hear anything. And is that
Potytail Haver
We still can't hear you still just to this minute. We still can't hear you
Okay, that was just me crashing. Oh, okay. That's what you were showing. Okay. But have you seen this one?
Here's me with the same important ball man, you know, they
Know I didn't know that
I want to see this the same and really do that. I need to see this. Let me see. Oh, you needed a gun
Don't see this
So far it's just like you yelling the best part is coming up. Hold on
I will hear him scream
Should have same importance bomb you might hear me scream. You understand
Just playing I mean, I don't see any poor bombs
I don't I guess it's gonna happen here. I guess he's gonna pop on
At least show us what we're waiting for the same and poor mom you were not
Yeah, here we go. Yeah. Oh, here's Alice McQueen. Who does that?
You're right. It's boring. Okay. So let's find the expensive. Oh, I saw right now. You're right. I saw it. I saw the poor mom
You're right. I did. So that's when he just came in. Okay. Damn. I saw a great little grateful
I'm grateful that I saw that poor mom
I
Like when you left earlier when I said something funny grateful, but please don't ever just like fake laugh like whoo
Like baby, I'm not
Yeah, but don't give me a fake laugh like who you know, I mean, I don't need that shit
Yeah, I got a giggle. Is that that's like a giggle. Oh, that's that's the one
That's the one. Oh
Single I have an X so I want to be single right now. Yes
You're there in there time to look for you in that picture
I heard say man porn by me and I'm gonna show oh my god. Is that be the Jesus Christ?
I just got scared for a minute. I was like, what the fuck is that?
He made a odd I
Was so drunk last time Peter was live and I did join but I was so wasted. Oh, you are
Yeah, I was I was like so shitty. I
Love I like be there. Come on guys. They're not wrong with be there
But she's she's mentally insane besides like her be a mentally insane. There's nothing yet. Is that right?
You know, well, we finally we all agree on something
You have a rumble you have a rumble I say can we
It's like psyche awakens or cult of psyche on rumble, but the trip came
I have a rumble too. It's called daddy's lair
So you can take that in your bubble daddy's lair. I didn't say that that was sick
That was jade dog. He was muted when he did this
Yeah, but like even if he wasn't unmuted he'd be like shine shine
I mean like we know what he's pretty much saying look looks like I wear 18 stars. I wear black jeans
Like we know what the motherfuckers say like who the fuck wears black denim jeans
Look inside he's a psyches cat. He's watching
Look, he's
They are the little sniveling smiling snowflakes. Oh, yeah, King Rob at least now King Rob actually says something
I made sense once it's fucking
Yeah, hey Rob bad on the back man. You actually said something that made sense. What's in your fucking gay look?
fucking freak
Sniveling, sniling, beta mods, you'll imagine modding for beta, like Jesus Christ.
Like all the drunk old ladies drinking again, I got to go mod for her, like I got better shit to do.
I got a life to live, like here goes their mob for this old cunt.
Oh, sorry about this.
That dog is cute, isn't that really, that's Christine's dog?
That's all the bounty hunter. It's not even a dog. It's a human being. No, the dog Christine her profile picture
She's on the bottom that dog in honor profile
Hunter
Marilyn Lee linen dog got like beat up by like five Hawaiians and they had to dive into the car
Like that niggas tried to always run their mouth and they met some fucking Hawaiians one time
Or some melons and them niggas fucking ran them fucking Harry dog. Oh, yeah, that's that. I am grateful
The dog is cute though
That's Christine. No, I know I like animals. I do rescues and stuff. So yeah, I'd love animals
She's beautiful
Christine I never do you're so hairy
What the hell is that?
That's a Pekingese in front of a volcano that he made for me.
It's an AI Pekingese and it's an AI picture with Pekingese.
That's what I use on my profile.
Is that Mustafa?
biscuit rollups. Oh, yeah. Fuck. Yeah, I make those things sometimes and I'm wasted. I know. My cheese. Oh, I'm not even wasted. I need that ball. But yeah, it's too late. The other day, when I was drawing, I made like three sausage biscuits, just eight. All of them. I got banned, so I went to go. All of them? You ate all three? It was two, but I just tried to brag.
Look at the chats going off tonight. I'm sending Christine dogs to Michael Vicks. If I was really hungry grateful
I'd eat up on you. Yeah, that's that
Right back guys. Tell for a second. We're back. Oh, okay
There's a Norwegian dog in the background with cinnamon roll. What is that whiskey?
It looks like a big mug of whiskey. It is
Look how happy that dog is, like I'm gonna eat this pretzel.
Very happy. He's gonna eat the pretzel and the mug.
He's gonna get drunk and look at the Norwegians in the background.
Yeah, I like the AIs that he makes.
Thank you so much. Yeah. Oh my gosh. Yeah.
Hey, guess what I have? I have like a whole thing of these.
If I can't get like, you know, drunk anymore.
Look at that.
Is that candy?
Yeah, candy.
Oh, yeah
They're so good I wake up and I eat these and I wake up and I have cavities
Actually, I lost like I had I have a tooth pulpit a couple years ago. Christine is a good woman. She looks like Caitlyn Jenner. I know
Caitlyn Jenner Caitlyn Jenner go on. Well ain't that a guy?
That was Bruce Jenner. It used to be Bruce Jenner. He's a woman now
Member like what is six foot tall guy that just joined like a woman's basketball team like I'm just gonna slay him talk to
Pogs. I'm a woman now. Like fuck you all
Memorowins like his shoulders were pointy. Oh, that's actually happening right now, sorry
I
Thought you were Johnny Depp when I joined the stream
air-conditioned this day and age
a friendly face on every page
Everything feels safe these days
The neighbors wave
The children play
The sunshine bright
The bills get paid
A perfect house
A perfect street
A perfect smile
This is all so fucking good!
This is the best part, please.
Oh, this is the best part.
Right here.
This is the best part, though.
Hey, he's got another beer.
He's got another beer.
Oh, please.
This is the smallest beer I've ever had since he was a kid.
It's so cold in here, I'm just gonna chill.
Hey guys, thank you so much for coming.
That was really good.
I was still going, sorry.
That's cool.
Always better than it looks, baby.
Switches are watching
That the wonder years
What is it from because that first picture looked like uh, the b-witch lady
Right. I mean, it's all AI. I mean
No, that's cool. I like that
That was a yeah, that was all a yeah, he's made in amongst these videos
I thought that was actually real video. I'm must be going crazy. No, that's what he's doing
Videos with a either he puts together
Well, I see it was just thank you
So you're saying that was a I okay? I wonder how he puts it together with the music
I don't know how, but I'll tell you right now what I'll put together. I'll put together a fucking casket, but I'm not the fucker
May may may not may not a I that's what
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
It's a it's it's a it's the hardest part
Once you already
I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little bit, I can show you like a little
I have two cigarettes left, and I'm going to smoke one of them with you guys, but look at the other two different colors.
That's how you can tell I'm not racist, because one of my cigarettes is brown and one is white.
Thank you.
What happened to Saiki? He picked on his mic.
that's fine because I'm vaping, that's what's happening, that's what I'm saying, it's up
to you.
Yeah, go ahead.
Okay.
Yes.
Thank you.
And I'm vaping.
Is that okay?
Whoa, don't blow that vape in my face.
I won't.
It's hybrid.
It's good.
It was the best you said smoke machine is that like from the floor like they have it today
At the club, so that kind of smoke on the stage is that
You know, yeah, you get what I'm gonna. Yeah
My brother does vapes so I said to him like you're basically sucking on the fog machine
What the hell is that?
What the hell am I looking at?
I don't know
Oh
He's doing an AI I think that is obviously a oh my goodness. What the fuck am I getting?
I
Like the arms. I like the size of my arms, but I don't know why I'm your arms. That's there. I
Wish I was talking grateful in that video
Who you hugging under who's that guy?
What the hell is that? Oh
He's kissing me
So give her a come on
Bro, don't disrespect me. He's like I come up here. Don't fuck. Yeah, I'm not with the guy
Ain't that rude grateful to be honest ain't that rude to make a video me kissing him? Yeah
That's fine if you wouldn't have sex with guys you're gay. That's one thing
But those that here make me have a kissing video. You're like, I'm not gay
Psyche, how about you Psyche and Prince William?
Oh
Member Prince Harry. Oh, that's actually not me. That's Harry
Thank you
I'm great tall though. Is he tall?
Ravel I'm grateful which is grateful grateful
Yeah, that is yeah, but yeah, he's I think he's tall though. Isn't he tall?
Prince Harry because I know I think his brother is Prince William
Prince Harry I would never really thought about it, but he's probably pretty tall like I've really never thought about
Also, Prince Harry is definitely shorter though. Like he's shorter. He's shorter. Yeah
Oh my god, what?
What am I watching?
psyche
Come on
He's making an AI
Do you have to go to bed? Gravel cuz it is
of the
I'm gonna mute myself while I piss and then we're not done pissing. I have two cigarettes left
I'd love if you stayed up here, but you'd mess with sucky and just chill out for like a night
Yeah, I'm watching the AI. I'm up. I'm up late. It's a weekend.
Whatever time it is, it's an hour and a half an hour or two.
Yeah, no, I'll be here in 30 minutes.
I'll be here in 30 minutes.
I'll be here myself when I use the restroom.
Okay.
We don't want to hear you, please.
Oh, you're going to sleep, huh, baby?
There's Prince Harry really six three if that's true, that's fucking crazy
Then how close Prince William?
Whoever in the chat said Prince Harry is six three
What is Prince William at least at least give us that so we know
Like don't just say one person site and not both of us
Oh, no Francis this guy like King Rob that like criminal
Black Rob that comes up here like I'm sorry
Rob racks like he comes up like I'm the only person that ever went to jail
I'm the best like I'm the biggest criminal here. Like you want to brag about being a criminal nigga
We don't care. We're up here that body. Yeah, Wayne up here to brag about golden
But I will lock grateful in my present if you get my drift
What about it? You're echoing kind of.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You made me feel, let's sing it to her.
This is like, you made me feel bare.
Oh no.
What do you mean you're bare for?
Yes, it was called
Access
Saw when you DJ wake up wake up. Yeah, and that's it the man. Yeah, me. I
DJ with the guy named Studer
He was the best
My uncle Charles
No, it was a music like music like it's like trance music again now they call it trance
Electric music now they call it electric music new wave they called it new wave
It's music. Yeah, the dance music dance music
But they call it trance now now it's called trance or electric they change it all the time
Every year mushrooms taste oh, I did
Like the shitty taste
Sweetheart Grable, this is one of my two cigarettes. I'm gonna lay it up for you, sweetheart
And then also I was getting the cones recently the the shroom cones
Yeah, I'm telling you that's the best the first time I tried it was in college
Yo, remember that fucking in a break
That Madonna wore that had metal combs remember the metal comb bra
Yeah, I remember that
Madonna Madonna. She's a couple years. She's a couple years. She's older than me. Remember when remember when she missed her
Yeah, I'm gonna suck around. I got one cigarette. Madonna Madonna.
This is the brand off. What do you say? Psych? Psych?
Mm-hmm
Season forever
Get a cigarette
Today's trend is brought to you by the number 6
Going out tonight, having a hit on our kids
Got my high heels on and you know the 6
You gotta see your face on top of two sticks
Flying so high in your life
It's 6
Tonight we're raising pain
And we'll do it all again, let the music play
That is cool, we're gonna go onward
And turn the bell, when we dance please
Thank you so much for watching!
Sign me, what else?
you. I think they're all guys.
Can you hear me? Yes. I can. I
can't hear you. I didn't have a
pleasure. It's all with you on
the panel tonight. I really did.
I'm sorry about this video.
Hell yeah, brother. Fuck the haters. This is Suggia Wiggas for life. Fuck the fucking haters.
I'm going to have to get a stronger hug the whole next summer.
A stronger hug the whole next summer.
I'm going to have to catch up with her.
it is
Barbecue sauce on a biscuit
It's like to lick off the sauce I
Can only use that on
Wings wings
I'd rather have wings than ribs. Well, ribs are good too, but have I had to choose like I'd rather have like buffalo wings.
Wings, because that's easy. Yeah, that's it.
There's this place near, there's a place called Charlie at Walmart near me, and they have the best Conan wings there.
It's barbecue, Korea. No, it's the best. It's really good. I'm hooked on those. I've only tried it like twice.
I've a crabs is not from Maryland, but one thing on their brain is like crawlfish like from New Orleans
Like I'll be we crawlfish, but they're probably like the same thing as crabs you get like a little tiny piece of meat
You're right it's like
Everybody's addicted to that here
No, no, no, I was actually born in New York
My mom was from South America. My dad was American and we were all
New York you ever meet salmon
No, I think I was there just a few months because my brother was born
No, we didn't live in that area part of New York Forest Hill
No, I'm a South American they're not they're not from that Central America or Puerto Rican is in the States now. That's not
Thank you
But we did stop there when we were coming back from South America to the states when I was a kid
Go back and forth on vacations
Oh
I remember like some of my friends would go to Merrill Beach and shit back in the day
But we always went to Ocean City, Maryland
It was the best like there was this thing called the shooting gallery
And it was like a mannequin and you shoot the fucking bullseye the fucking mannequin play the piano
I'm making the sandwich
No, seriously, just something fucking remember that little twisty thing that's around your bread. I just took it all
No, my cat
The youngest one
You have so cute cute. He's right here
Her name I gave her name is Dara, but I call her baby. She's like a baby to me. She acts like one
Yeah, I rescued her it was around September or
October of 2024 so she's around to
One time I remember last year. I don't know where you're from, but it was so much snow and ice on the ground
It was like it snowed and then it was like ice for two weeks and I felt so bad over those cats
But now that the summer is back when I walk over the land bridge
Uh-huh. See the cat
Please you guys survive good. I mean
They can they survive a lot
Mm-hmm. Hey, you know is Ashley top of the deals my girl Jim Nick. You got a new liver
She was I heard that so I'm happy for her. So she really got it
She got a month. I hope she never drinks again
Well, you never know. I hope she does
Well, no, she'll lose that liver.
I was just kidding.
I'm happy for her, I'm glad.
Come on.
Yeah, no, really I do
I mean, that's my best fucking friend Jim
Please yeah, not yeah that no do not be that's my best
No, what do you mean? I'm not being rude. I said I'm glad for her
I'm happy that she got a new liver. You know that he takes care of it
She better take me like that's why the Rolling Stones are like 90 and still like singing songs like they probably got like so many
Livers like Keith Richards
I'd say four livers.
My uncle, he died of, you know,
he had liver infection or whatever
because of alcoholism.
It destroyed his liver.
Yo, sometimes grateful, I'm only 42, it's not that old.
But like sometimes I think I'm 22 and like,
oh, it's all good, I just drink beer every day.
But like, bro, I don't want to die, understand?
Yeah, or slow down slow down
Oh, I'm speeding up
You don't do that. That's what my uncle did and look what happened. It's his liver
His liver gave out on him
Because of alcohol
When I was a little kid my mom used to make liver for dinner
My mom too, I hated liver
Me my brother be outside playing I'm her mom
Time for dinner or whatever like she's screaming and me my brother like oh, we got to go home guys like we don't my mom
Was gonna like punish us
Yeah, my mom
But I hated liver I barely ate it I wouldn't hardly touch it but she'd like liver and that's why she'd like to make liver
And then like put it in like a paper towel. I'm like, oh, look at this member. Oh membersparagus. Oh
No, I hate asparagus and anything green except for lettuce
Okra okra can't stand okra
Oh my god, I cannot stand okra win free. You're right
Okay, so it was nasty. Yeah, it was horrible. You know what sucks that you're married grateful?
I thought you were single. No, I was married and uh and I ended that other I don't want to get married
again. I like to be on my own and you know see who I want to see I just don't want to commit it
Yeah, no to marriage
Once almost a second time
And it's like no
What about lost
Yeah, of course, that's normal, but you'll have to be married
What about love?
I don't think I know how to love. I'm Syriacist. Not like that.
I love animals, family, but not being loved.
I think I was that first time, but no, I'm probably not capable of being in love.
I'm in love.
and stay safe and stay safe not not commit yourself to somebody and then it
don't work out you never know you never know okay yeah yeah where is psyche what
he's making another AI he's making another
I'm tired of pretending that I don't love you anymore.
I got to take the chance or let it pass by.
My cat is staring. He's like staring at my phone like what the hell or what are we listening to?
This is only one piece because and the two burritos you ate two burritos
Yeah, I mean you can say you got the munchies
Let's just sit here wait till slaggy comes back
We know you're there watching us
And then at least we could see his
Like give us a look at like go boys like Jesus Christ
Where did he go?
Rudy and Lenore he does has a very nice
He does
He does. They're all so cute. They're also I'm not even a cat lover
But when I see sucky's beautiful cats like I'm like come on
This is this is why I know Jesus Christ is real and I know God is real when I see sucky
I never knew God was a real thing
actually
Where did he go?
He said he was coming right back
People say a lot of things up here. I'll do one more. You ever eat these oh
Sweetest fish. Oh, what is that? What is that candy? I've never seen those
Oh
What about a little sour patch?
Store bursts, I mean, I'm fucked my teeth are gonna be brought down
We're trying to hold it down psyche, what are you doing here you have abandoned us
Hey, I have I had a lot of fun told you I mean I hope I hope you had as much fun as I have
Yeah
We had a good night. We're having a good night. We had nothing but rain all day Joe is it was pouring down and all day
They said we're gonna have a tropical
Tomorrow we got rain in the forecast or like whatever you where you
Well right now in Texas, I mean in Texas right now
Terry funk
We get we got a lot of rain in the forecast tomorrow. I try to go jogging or walking a couple days a couple miles every day
Yeah
They keep saying we're gonna get flooded but some areas got flooded but we haven't out here just rains the lawn and then stop
Stop it. It's every day now again. It was nice. It was beautiful the other day. I was out in the pool
And then on Sun since yesterday
You remember the bonaris
No, I don't remember that I've lived in a lot of different places over these two so no
But how long ago was that because I've been here since college
Oh, okay. No, I was I was I was I was parting too hard
Ain't going to call it
When the college and then I was parting a lot
We were a part of your back in the day. Oh hell. Yes
Yeah
No, I was pretty wild
Everybody was
We're not Stella. I ain't had nobody to settle me down
Well, no, no, I get think we're too young man. I don't want to get married young at
19 and my parents had it annulled
Oh, you're married. I'm sorry. No, I said I was they had it or no, so they ended it
That was the only marriage I didn't want to get married I almost again afterwards. It's no
Because I've seen some marriages go bad, you know as a kid, so I didn't want that
I think if I marry you
Uh, no, I don't want to get married. Period. I already did it. It was a no, but I just feel free. I like to be, um,
I'm from my own.
Your memories will be children of the corn.
Yes, I remember that it was a long time ago. Yes
It would be cool if like we were dating you just like come over and watch it we need like
You still have the movies what you got him in the you you have them
You have them I have them in here. Oh
You remember Chucky though, yes now that I watched all of them. Yes. I did watch all yes
Children of the corner. They go we see one
Never when Chucky went to a military camp
He's like ollie ollie oxen-free and how about his bribe his bride
That was the last
To be honest grateful, but you're pretty you're fucking cool with shit like I'm at fucking mungo dude
I only have one cigarette left, so I ain't gonna be here anymore.
You know, that's just like, I need to see how much of my life works.
Yeah, like, the Chucky, I think, aren't they coming out with another movie, I think?
Another movie, I think?
Probably.
I heard something about it.
Nothing's out yet.
Member Michael Voorhees.
Hold on.
Which movie was he from?
Michael
Myers okay, Myers. I know yes the Halloween
Remember these. Oh, yeah, that's it. Yeah, I
Like the Halloween movie
Well, we try to say the Halloween movies till like Halloween time
That's when I like to watch him it during the Halloween time
Yeah, like if you watch them all year long, it'll be won't be like new so I got trying to save them. Mm-hmm. I'm grateful
Mm-hmm. I wish you'd live near me. I'll invite you over and we can watch
Halloween and you know what I get I can download any movies with the extra torrents
So I've got a bunch of movies that I have from a long time ago that I got not long during COVID
Are they porno's no no not porno's movies like yeah, like
Everything from the 80s 90s. Yeah, there's the best movie
Oh my god, they remember the goonies back to the future. Yes. I have that I have
There's three back to you
Yes, I got a fine. I can find the other one and get it. It's easy to get
Remember the third one like they're in the wall wall West and like bitch is like
I think that's the one that I think that's the one that I didn't get that one
And what did Molly Ringwald, maybe I had a friend in college and we're still friends and she looks just like Molly Ringwald and still does and still does.
Molly Ringwald was in fucking, hold on, remember the movie, The Great Outdoors? I don't think Molly Ringwald was in that, but she should have been.
Oh, really? Who was in that one? I don't think I saw that. I didn't see that movie.
There was like Dan Agroid and John Candy and some other lady and some other kids.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, and I had, I thought Rob Lowe was hot. I watched all his movies.
He still is. He's still is. Yeah, Dan right. He is. Remember how he lived?
The way he's the most beautiful actor
He was in my one of my favorite TV shows
No, I didn't know he did
And he has he has a brother and the brother isn't a cute
Are you serious? Yes, that's his brother Chablow and he's not cute like him at all
He's ugly
He's he yeah, kind of but compared to him. Yes
Just imagine your brother's so hot like all my brother's Rob low and I'm Chad low like what a fucking ass
Yeah, I don't think he made too many movies
but it was Chad Lowe. And they're related. They're daddy and attorney. Sweetheart,
can you see me or hear me? Yes, I hear you. This is the latest cigarette I have in my entire house.
Now I'm gonna smoke it with you. I've had it three times. It's all to you. I really don't think we had that phone.
Yeah, that's a big cigarette. That's a big cigarette.
Oh, it's a 100. You're damn right. It's a big cigarette.
I don't smoke cigarettes. I just smoke cigarettes. I just smoke weed or muscle.
Yeah, I put a drink with a sparkle beer.
then i wouldn't drink this purple beer oh i thought it was uh pet what is it
it was it was pepper fist ball it was a joke it was like a joke
hey joe come we do that for you stomach it's like my stomach it's better
do one thing i always do think about is i would love to go back to my middle school and like
elementary school and like walk like see the old classrooms they used to go to
Nowadays with so many new year's like they would never like I'm like hey
I used to go here. Let me walk the halls. They were like oh, I did that. It's it. It looks so small
I did that every time
It was in Overland Park, Kansas.
I was a little kid and we lived there for two and a half years
before going back overseas.
And I went to visit that place and I had my dogs with me.
And Joe, it looks so small to me.
Like the playground looks small.
And when I'm walking around in the pool, it just looks smaller.
Why?
When I did use to go back to Marl Park,
I remember like I could take my two arms
And then put my other arm out and like touch like the walls. I'm like damn when I was a little kid
It's like it's the biggest school ever not gonna touch the fucking walls
But that's what I felt like that just probably because I was an adult when I when I visited
And I was little then I think I was like I was eight
And it just seems small it was like
Where'd you say you're from the repair line or something yeah, no, I was born I was born in New York
My brother was born in Coral Gable
Miami
My sister was born in Bolivia, because when we went back over there, and then my youngest brother,
and they have dual citizenship, and my younger brother in the United States, my dad's an American.
He was American
No, my dad was he worked for mobile oil an oil man
He'd make great money. Yeah, so we lived everywhere
No, not military oil all business like like mobile like mobile
That's what we work for they have Chevron
They used to have Gulf oil. All those oil companies, Conoco, the people that worked
way up in the offices. We was just, yeah, so he had a great job with them. So we lived overseas
and had the best vacations paid for by them. Where were you at or where would you go on vacations,
babe? Like where I want to hear about your... You know one place I've never been? I've been to
or traveled and visited but I have never been to Hawaii and that's here I've
never been to Hawaii that's what I want to go and visit and that's right here I've
been so far away to so many places but never been to Hawaii
Calm down. Let me just say this. Get on my bus. The reason I would never go to Hawaii is I would never get on an airplane
Like I'm being dead serious and I don't even like boats
So if I wish if I did ever did you say I did was Daniel
You're like, I want to go to Hawaii. I'm like, you know what? See you. I got it. We're breaking up
I can't do it. I hated planes too, but I was a little kid and I had a
fly with my family
I mean, these are like nine or 12 hour flights. We even lived in Tokyo, but I was uh, I was a toddler
I've never flown on an airplane in my entire 42 years old. I've never I hated it Joe
I hated it. It was especially the long flights especially for a little kid
It was I couldn't sleep in the plane. I'd be terrified. I thought we'd crash or something
Because we hit the turbulence that we'd hit the turbulence sometimes
And then it starts shaking ship. Yes
And we were we were over the wrecked at whatever the devil's
Rectangle we were going to Florida from South America
Yes, there's something there and it's just we hit that and we traveled that many times
But we hit the turbulent one time and the whole plane took and we freaked out
Oh my god, I was fucking freak out. Oh, and that's why they want to get on the plane again
We're just settling that we're gonna fucking fly.
Yes, that's the one, the triangle, not the, not the, not the, what is it, the, uh, the other one, the smaller one, whatever, diamond one or whatever they call it, and, and after that we were, yeah, and that was, uh, and I thought that was gonna be the end of it.
And so we're in the States for a while and then I went to high and yeah
I was I was about to go to high school and then we had to go back overseas and
When we got to the airport Joe, I was crying because I told my parents I don't want to go. Can I can you leave me here?
It's like I really I was I was scared
It's like no I can't do this anymore
Yeah, when we were kids, my friends Samantha and her sister, they like will put them on
a plane and they would go visit their grandma in Florida and like their parents wouldn't
even fly.
We don't they would just put them on the plane.
I'm never being a little kid and thinking about them.
I know I saw that before the movie and I was grateful.
My parents never did that to us, never.
We have a big cigarette.
You're going to light it up.
We can't sit up here and flirt all night long.
Come on.
No, no, I'm going to go to bed pretty soon.
It's going to be nice out.
It rained all damn day.
It's going to be nice out all night long.
So I want to have a good day tomorrow, and I'll stay till you finish out.
I'm still vaping.
Thank you.
I thought that you were very vocal.
Yeah, and you know what my bucket list I think is going to be I don't know if they have this Joe anymore
but I remember they had it years ago
where you can buy this pass for people that are roller coaster addicts
And they take you to Europe and they take you to Europe and take you to the best roller coaster rides all over Europe for the whole summer
Do you like roller coasters or not? Yes, I'm a roller coaster theme. Yes. I've ridden so many old roller coasters everywhere. I mean
Slags over Texas
Afterworld they had a nice roller coaster, but I've seen some better ones over seas
but they could be dangerous
I thought he was gonna do an AI or something and he said I'll be maybe he fell asleep
Yeah, yeah, we are
So how's the weather where you're at is it bad like here
You men in this ship
No, it's just I'm worried about all this rain, man. I'm telling you it's been so bad every other day
Last week it was every day
I'm usually so busy pumping iron that I really
Mean it's it's pretty bad it was pretty bad here
Lately especially because they said that we're gonna have a tropical. We're gonna have tropical storms this summer. It could be a hurricane
And this is how it's done
If you ever come visit me, I'll buy you crawfish or like crabs. Well, crawfish crabs crab legs
You know what up a crab crawfish bean and crab legs bean and I haven't had any of that since over a year ago
Spana crab legs
You what you really do like crawfish for? Yes, I do my my brother and my best friend got me hooked on it
Not my best friend. That was a friend of mine that passed away a couple years ago
Remember when they steamed them up with shrimp and like peppers and stuff
Yeah, did you say shrimp? No, no
You don't like shrimp not with crawfish
Yeah, but remember when they do like a big crawfish boil and it's like crawfish and shrimp and potatoes and onions
Never not here. It's always just crawfish potatoes
And corn
Yes, a little the ones cut up like they're cutting half
Do you always go on the battle? Are you Karen? Are you in X? Yes? I said I was I next
Yes, you did that before
I'm grateful now because I changed my name
Last year after I got clear and I almost lost my life last year so so things change
Yeah
Oh, wow, that's a big secret it looks like it
To 200 to 100 I thought I recognized your boys are like hold on there
Yes, it's me
What what did you don't say? What's it me? I'm the one that says what you don't want me
I said I fun talking to you. Oh, yeah. No, I know
We're having a chat
And nothing wrong with it
And psyche fell asleep
Do you know what? He missed out then and he didn't got any of our problems and our fucking problems didn't motherfuckin' bother sleep.
He's making up. I guess he's doing more of the AI.
Psyche, where are you? Psyche, where are you?
Psyche, it's not. He's making more AI. You're probably right. He probably is like writing lyrics. He's like typing the lyrics and like, oh man, man, man.
Oh, he does put the music together with a lot of it AI videos
Great boys out baby girl. Thank you. Yeah, it was pleasure talking. Okay. Yeah, you too
I'm gonna crash so I gotta get up early and psyche you have a good night
What when you crash out, can you dream of me?
I'm not gonna dream. I'm gonna fit a smoke in this vape, and then I'm gonna
Know a lot of people don't like it, but I think you're
Like me. No, it's just a couple troublemakers
Lie and then some one person putting old stuff back all the time when she's gonna have a lot of the recent stuff
Okay, well you have a good night Joe and you too